[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the meaning of the term graminivore?", "correct_answer": "an animal that feeds on grass", "incorrect_answers": ["an animal that feeds on fruit", "an animal that feeds on seaweed", "an animal that feeds on tree leaves"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Napoleon Dynamite, what was the name of the farmer who shot the cow and lives across from Napoleon?", "correct_answer": "Lyle", "incorrect_answers": ["Jeb", "Mike", "Tucker"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Botophobia is the term used for the fear of crowds.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Why does Paulie think Rocky wants to fight again in Rocky Balboa?", "correct_answer": "Hes mad they took down his statue.", "incorrect_answers": ["Hes bored.", "He thinks he can beat the heavyweight champion.", "He has a brain tumor."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This very old cat breed, which occurred naturally in Turkey, has a slender body with medium length fur, usually white.", "correct_answer": "Turkish Angora", "incorrect_answers": ["Ocicat", "Cymric", "Selkirk Rex"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these is the study of cells?", "correct_answer": "cytology", "incorrect_answers": ["protozoology", "cellogy", "ecology"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What Academy Award-winning actress received the Golden Raspberry Award for Worst Actress for the 1981 movie Mommie Dearest?", "correct_answer": "Faye Dunaway", "incorrect_answers": ["Meryl Streep", "Whoopi Goldberg", "Jane Fonda"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This animal is the heaviest member of its family, and also one of the smallest marine mammals.", "correct_answer": "Sea otter", "incorrect_answers": ["Sea pig", "Polar mouse", "None of these"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Malaleuca alternifolia is the Latin name of this plant.", "correct_answer": "Tea tree", "incorrect_answers": ["Sandalwood", "Peppermint", "Lavender"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many body parts does Obi-Wan cut off Anakin in the Battle of the Heroes in Star Wars: Episode 3?", "correct_answer": "3", "incorrect_answers": ["4", "2", "1"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Homers epic poems, The Iliad and The Odyssey, are made up of this many books each.", "correct_answer": "24", "incorrect_answers": ["3", "61", "15"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these organs is responsible for the production of blood proteins, including clotting proteins?", "correct_answer": "Liver", "incorrect_answers": ["Bone marrow", "All of these", "Spleen"]}]